// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: " Which of the following property is used to set the background image of an element ?",
  answer: "background-image",
  options: [
    "background-repeat",
    " background-position",
    "background-image",
    "background-color"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: " Which of the following property is used to increase or decrease the size of a font ?",
  answer: "font-size",
  options: [
    "font-weight",
    "font",
    "font-size",
    "None of the above"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "  Which of the following property is used to set the width of an image border ?",
  answer: "border",
  options: [
    "width-of-border",
    "img-width",
    " border-width-img",
    "border"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: " Which of the following property changes the color of top border ?",
  answer: ":border-top-color",
  options: [
    ":border-left-color",
    ":border-top-color",
    " :border-bottom-color",
    ":border-right-color"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "Which of the following property serves as shorthand for the marker properties ?",
  answer: " list-style",
  options: [
    " list-style",
    "list-style-image",
    "list-style-position",
    "list-style-type"
  ]
},
// you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
// but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
 {
  numb: 6,
question: "Which of the following value of cursor shows it as an arrow ?",
answer: "default",
 options: [
   "crosshair",
  "pointer",
    " move",
   "default"
 ]
},
{
numb: 7,
question: " CSS stands for.",
answer: " Cascading Style Sheets",
options: [
 "Control Style Sheets",
"Common Style Sheets",
  " Central Style Sheets",
 " Cascading Style Sheets"
]
},
{
numb: 8,
question: " Which of the following property specifies the right padding of an element ?",
answer: " padding-right",
options: [
 "padding-top",
"padding-left",
  "padding-bottom",
 " padding-right"
]
},
{
numb: 9,
question: " Which of the following property changes the style of bottom border ?",
answer: " :border-bottom-style",
options: [
 ":border-left-style",
" :border-right-style",
  " :border-bottom-style",
 ":border-top-style"
]
},
{
numb: 10,
question: " Which of the following is the first web browser ?",
answer: " :margin-top",
options: [
 " :margin-top",
":margin-left",
  ":margin-bottom",
 ":margin"
]
},
{
numb: 11,
question: " Which of the following property is used to set the background image of an element ?",
answer: "background-image",
options: [
 "background-position",
"background-repeat",
  "background-color",
 "background-image"
]
},
{
numb: 12,
question: "Which of the following selector matches a element based on its class attribute ?",
answer: "The Class Selector",
options: [
 "The Descendant Selector",
"The Class Selector",
  " The Universal Selector",
 "The Type Selector"
]

},
{
numb: 13,
question: "Which of the following property is used to change the face of a font ?",
answer: " font-family",
options: [
 "font-variant",
" font-weight",
  " font-family",
 " font-style"
]
},
{
numb: 14,
question: " Which of the following property is used to set the text shadow around a text ?",
answer: " text-shadow",
options: [
 "white-space",
"text-decoration",
  " text-shadow",
 " text-transform"
]
},
{
numb: 15,
question: "Which of the following is correct about RGB Values format of CSS colors ?  ",
answer: " All of the above.",
options: [
 "This property takes three values, one each for red, green, and blue.",
"This color value is specified using the rgb( ) property.",
  "The value can be an integer between 0 and 255 or a percentage.",
 " All of the above."
]
},
{
numb: 16,
question: "How many types of levels in style sheets ?",
answer: " three level",
options: [
 "two level",
"One level",
  " four level",
 " three level"
]
},
{
numb: 17,
question: "An external style sheet is ideal when the style is applied to",
answer: "many pages",
options: [
 "many pages",
"few pages",
  "single pages",
 "None of the above"
]
},
{
numb: 18,
question: " Which of the style sheet is also known as Embedded Style Sheet ?",
answer: "Document Style Sheet",
options: [
 "Inline Style Sheet",
"External Style Sheet",
  "Document Style Sheet",
 "None of the above"
]
},
{
numb: 19,
question: "Which of the following is the superior styles of html ?",
answer: " css",
options: [
 "frame",
"frames",
  "iframe",
 " css"
]
},
{
numb: 20,
question: " The Disadvantages of Cascading Style Sheets is",
answer: "Browsers Compatibility",
options: [
 "Low Performance",
"Browsers Compatibility",
  "High Performance",
 "All of the above"
]
},
];